<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<wordlist>
  <word show="abdominally">
    <phonetic></phonetic>
    <meanings>[]</meanings>
    <eg>['The surgery may be approached abdominally, vaginally, or as a laparoscopically assisted vaginal procedure.', '该手术可经腹、经阴道，或可在腹腔镜辅助下经阴道进行。', 'The hope is to identify and treat those people at greatest risk for becoming abdominally obese.', '由此希望能够识别并治疗那些容易变成大肚汉的高危人群。', 'Managing Experience of 62 Patients Whose Abdominally Injury Combined With Multiple Injuries', '以腹部伤为主的多发伤62例救治体会']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abattoir">
    <phonetic>美 ['æbə.twɑr] 英 ['æbə.twɑː(r)] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['n.〈外〉屠宰场', '网络: 屠场；角斗场；屠宰厂']</meanings>
    <eg>['Russian soldiers were trampling up and down on the corpses, dragging their latest victims into position like butchers in an abattoir.', '俄国士兵踩在尸体上像屠宰场的屠夫一样把刚刚遇害的人拖到坑里。', "Not the aftermath of a battle as I've known it, but a bloody abattoir of rent limbs and torn and eaten flesh.", '这不是我所熟悉的一场大战之后的战场，而是一场充斥着残肢和血肉的大屠杀。', 'Beneath me , this awful city. It screams like an abattoir full of retarded children. . . and the night reeks of fornication and bad.', '我下面的城市，就像充满尖叫的智障儿童的屠宰场…在夜晚到处都是奸情与罪恶。', 'One day he hopes to also lure the bankers to his farm in Yorkshire for farming classes and a visit to the abattoir.', '威尔逊希望，有一天，他也能够把银行家们吸引到他在约克郡的农场，让他们在那里学习耕作并参观屠宰场。', 'The business location is about a mile outside the town, but vehicles have to drive through a residential area to reach the abattoir.', '这家屠宰场虽然离城镇有一英里，可是来这里的汽车必需经过一片住宅区。', 'The major cause of this predicament is the lack of funds to put and maintain an abattoir.', '主要原因这一困境是缺乏资金，付诸表决，并保持一个屠场。', 'Others would be rounded up and sent to an abattoir for either human or pet consumption.', '其它骆驼将被赶到一起，送进屠宰场，制成人或宠物的食品。', 'Education in hygienic food handling for abattoir workers and raw meat producers is essential to keep contamination to a minimum.', '向屠宰厂工人以及生肉生产商开展卫生食品操作方面的教育，对于尽可能降低污染程度至关重要。', 'When I first saw abattoir in a book I thought it was the most beautiful word in the world.', '当我第一次在书中看到“屠宰场”我认为这是世界上最美丽的词儿。', 'So PETA required that web cameras should be installed immediately in every abattoir still receiving Australian cows and sheep.', '因此该组织称，在所有接收澳大利亚活牛活羊的国外屠宰场安装网络摄像头已经刻不容缓。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abduction">
    <phonetic>美 [æb'dʌkʃ(ə)n] 英 [æb'dʌkʃ(ə)n] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['n.外展(作用)；诱拐', '网络: 绑架；在劫难逃；劫持']</meanings>
    <eg>['He goes on to claim that the purpose of his alleged abduction was to discredit Iran and its nuclear program.', '接着他声称，绑架他的目的是为了诋毁伊朗以及其核项目。', "She spoke of her abduction, of how she was taken to one of the residences of Moammar Gadhafi's soldiers.", '她说出了（卡扎菲支持者）对她的诱骗，关于她是怎么被卡扎菲的士兵带出其中一个处所。', 'He says Pyongyang has also failed to investigate the past abduction of Japanese nationals by North Korean agents, as it had promised to do.', '他说，平壤在调查北韩间谍过去绑架日本国民问题上没有遵守它曾作出的承诺。', 'Her relatives do not know, after the abduction of a woman that I am not in trouble?', '她的亲人都不知道，以后说我拐骗妇女不就麻烦了？', 'Bloggers without a high profile on the international stage are especially vulnerable to intimidation, abduction and worse, he said.', '他说，在国际上名气不大的博客作者特别容易受到恐吓、绑架或更恶劣的对待。', 'The Afghan Islamic Press news agency said the Taliban insurgents were responsible for the abduction.', '阿富汗伊斯兰通讯社报道，塔利班武装分子对此次绑架事件负责。', 'Abduction stabilizer bar between legs is never used as a handle to turn the child.', '千万不能用两腿之间保持外展的支持棒给小儿翻身。', 'He ticked off seven troubling events over the last month, including the abduction of four of his men.', '他简略的描述了上个月发生的七次令人烦恼的事件，其中就包括他的四个人被绑架的情况。', "No suspects have been arrested in connection with the abduction and killing of a local politician's supporters and media entourage.", '对于这起绑架并杀害当地政界人士支持者和记者的事件，目前尚未逮捕任何嫌疑人。', 'There is no statement of any organization or person creating the abduction incident.', '目前尚无任何组织或个人声明制造了这起绑架事件。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abdominal">
    <phonetic>美 [æb'dɑmɪn(ə)l] 英 [æb'dɒmɪn(ə)l] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['adj.腹部的', 'n.腹肌', '网络: 腹部前屈机；腹部训练器；腹的']</meanings>
    <eg>['Result Forty-two cases were all cured, 3 cases incision infection. There was no abdominal abscess, incision fistula or other complication.', '结果本组全部治愈，感染3例，未出现吻合口瘘及腹腔脓肿并发症。', 'If you are planning on getting pregnant, you should be very cautious about the placement of any tattoo near the abdominal area.', '如果你正在计划怀孕，要非常谨慎地考虑任何腹部的纹身。', 'The patient appetite waste away, dry mouth smell, the surface of the tongue with a yellow moss, often accompanied by abdominal pain.', '病人食欲废绝，口腔干燥发臭，舌面覆有黄白苔，常伴有腹痛。', 'For a new analgesia which is cheap, highly effective and easy to manipulate normatively, we would prefer Abdominal Acupuncture.', '为了探索一种价格低廉、起效迅速、操作规范的新的镇痛方法，我们选择了腹针疗法。', 'One of the easiest ways to get six pack abs involves burning off the body fat that covers the abdominal muscles.', '打造腹肌最简单的方法之一就是燃烧覆盖在腹部肌肉上的脂肪。', 'A menstrual blood from the little cavity of residual horn filled progressively the salpinx, which had abdominal ostium closed.', '从残留的小喇叭逐步填补输卵管，其中有过腹部口闭腔经血。', 'close your eyes, rub his hands forced, over his eyes, while deep breathing, abdominal breathing with relaxation, breath tightened.', '闭上眼睛，两手用力搓热，遮住眼睛，还深呼吸，腹部共同吸气放松，呼气收紧。', '"Sitting on it requires that you don\'t slouch, which is great for your back and works your abdominal muscles all day long, " she said.', '坐在训练球上，你就没办法驼背了，一整天都可以训练背部和腹部肌肉。', 'The presence of hepatic fibrosis seems to be associated with known host and viral factors as well as the presence of abdominal obesity.', '肝纤维化的存在可能与已知的宿主和病毒因素以及腹部肥胖有关。', 'In September he reached the semi finals of the US Open but this time it was an abdominal injury that prevented him playing his best.', '九月豆子闯进了美网的半决赛，而这次阻止他前进的是腹部的伤势。很明显，我们大爱黄豆。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abed">
    <phonetic>美 [ə'bed] 英 [ə'bed] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['adv.在床上', '网络: 阿拜德；阿贝德；阿比德']</meanings>
    <eg>['"Lucky for you we were dicing, and not abed yet, " said the man who\'d opened the door.', '“算你运气，我们正在玩骰子呢，还没去睡，”开门的那个人说。', 'Abed Rabu said the most important thing for the Palestinians is to see what the United States and Israel plan to do.', '拉布说，对巴勒斯坦人而言，最重要的是看到美国和以色列将计划做什么。', 'Since he officially handed power to his vice president, Abed Rabbo Mansour al-Hadi, on Wednesday, Mr. Saleh has hardly faded from the scene.', '自从周三萨勒交权给副总统艾尔哈迪以来，他几乎没有从政治舞台引退。', 'Abed - la said that in the next two days, Hamas militants have been forcing their family to stay downstairs.', '阿贝德-拉波说，在接下来的两天时间里，哈马斯武装人员一直强迫他们一家人继续呆在楼下。', 'They were not allowed to lie long abed in the mornings, but the old lady had them up and doing as soon as the cock crew.', '两个仆人早上不能睡懒觉，因为这老妇人要求他们每天鸡叫的时候就起床干活儿。', 'Last week, gunmen near Mosul killed Suha Abed Allah, a veterinarian running as a member of a multisectarian alliance.', '上周，摩苏尔附近的持枪歹徒杀害了苏哈·阿贝德·阿拉，一位参选的来自多世俗联盟的素食主义者。', '"Stock markets and real estate markets are doing well but that\'s momentum investing. It is not a great new opportunity, " says Mr Abed.', '“股市和房地产市场固然一片繁荣，但那是跟风投资，不是什么了不起的新机会，”阿比德先生说。', '"They will not leave, " said Abed Sahib Mohammed Hadi, an elderly man in a beige suit.', '“他们不会离开，说：”阿比德穆罕默德萨赫比哈迪，一名老人在米色西装。', 'Each morning they lay abed till the breakfast bell, pleasantly conscious that there were no efficient wives to rouse them.', '每天早晨，他们都赖到早餐铃响才起床，愉快地意识到没有管得宽的妻子来催促。', 'Abed left his comfortable life and returned to a remote area of northeastern Bangladesh.', '他放弃了自己舒适的生活，返回偏远的孟加拉东北地区。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abdicate">
    <phonetic>美 英 ['æbdɪkeɪt] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['v.退(位)；让(位)；辞(职)；【法律】废(嫡)', '网络: 放弃；让位；退位']</meanings>
    <eg>['He made the choice to abdicate because, as supreme governor of the Church of England, he was not permitted to marry a divorced woman.', '他选择放弃王位是因为身为英国教会的最高领袖，他不可以与离婚女子结婚。', 'the nation was thrilled, shocked and sympathetic. whether he would abdicate in favor of his brother became the question of the hour.', '举国上下都感到激动，震惊。放弃王位，支持他的兄弟当前热门话题。', "Ask for help, don't abdicate responsibility or tough it out yourself: I learned this lesson very early on in my project management career.", '寻求帮助，不要推卸责任，也不要委屈了自己：我在项目经理这个职位上很早就知道了这一点。', 'The British wanted another candidate to run Zanzibar, and demanded the nephew abdicate.', '英国人心中另有人选，要求发动政变的侄子让位。', "But expensive things are not inevitably the province of the rich unless we abdicate society's power of choice.", '但是，昂贵的东西并不必然该省丰富的，除非我们放弃社会的选择权。', "But expensive things are inevitably the province of the rich unless we abdicate society's power of choice.", '然而，只要你不放弃对社会权利的选择，高档享受不可避免地成为富人的特有的领域。', 'But the expensive things are not inevitably the province of the rich unless we abdicate the power of the choice.', '但是，昂贵的东西并非一定属于富人，除非我们放弃了选择的权力。', 'He attempted to carry out military reforms, but the civil party was too strong for him and he was forced to abdicate.', '他试图进行军事改革，但是官僚贵族派系的力量对他来说太过于强大，因而他被迫退位。', 'They will be forced to abdicate their self made thrones as the era of darkness falls away to make room for fresh rays of light.', '它们将被迫放弃它们自制的宝座，因为黑暗时代要消逝来给新生的光芒腾出空间。', 'He then returned home, only to be forced to abdicate by the communists a month later.', '回到家，一个月后，他被共产党强迫退位。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abash">
    <phonetic>美 [ə'bæʃ] 英 [ə'bæʃ] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['v.使…脸红', '网络: 使羞愧；使局促不安；使困窘']</meanings>
    <eg>['If I had not known before that you were trying somehow to abash me I should know it now.', '如果我以前不知道你老是挖苦我，那么现在我知道了。', 'That could abash the little bird That kept so many warm.', '能够使得小鸟不安保有此多暖意。', 'That could abash the little bird.', '能使小巧的鸟儿备受伤害。', 'Embarrass Nothing can abash him.', '没有什么能使他感到惭愧。', 'Would you like to buy some UV protect cosmetic for them if the man you know feel abash to buy it himself?', '你身边有这样的男士吗？你会为他买防晒品吗？', 'abash: cause to feel self-conscious or embarrassed', '使局促不安；使困窘']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abdomen">
    <phonetic>美 ['æbdəmən] 英 ['æbdəmən] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['n.肚子；下腹部；【虫类】腹部', '网络: 腹腔']</meanings>
    <eg>['For women, this might be especially true after menopause, when body fat tends to shift from the arms, legs and hips to the abdomen.', '对于更年期之后的女性而言更为普遍，她们的脂肪从手臂、腿部、臀部逐渐游移到小腹上。', 'She catches her breath and lies back down on the bed, her hand resting protectively on her abdomen.', '她吸了口气又躺了下来，他的手保护性的放在腹部。', 'Today does plays the matter, I which the mood relaxes suddenly felt abdomen twitches, I rush to with great speed the restroom solution!', '今天做玩事，心情放松的我突然感觉腹部一阵抽搐，我火速赶往厕所解决！', "Finally, doctors found a tumor in Saoirse's abdomen. She was in stage four of a malignant cancer called neuroblastoma.", '最后，医生在西尔莎•罗南的腹部发现了肿瘤。她得的是一种恶性肿瘤，叫做神经母细胞瘤。', 'The pain of appendicitis may be referred to any region of the abdomen.', '阑尾炎的疼痛可能涉及腹部的任何部位。', 'How much cardio does it take to burn through that stubborn layer of fat lingering around your abdomen?', '到底要多久的有氧训练，才会开始燃烧那些在你的腹部囤积已久的脂肪？', 'The second slash was low on the abdomen. This wound had not been meant to kill; it had served an entirely different purpose.', '第二处位于下腹部，这个伤口虽然不是致命伤，但却代表了另一种特别的意义。', "Place the baby on the mother's abdomen or, if the cord is long enough (don't tug at it), on her chest.", '把宝宝放在妈咪的腹部，如果脐带足够长（不要强行拉扯），就放在胸部。', 'In his hands, the body slowly carried from the bed surface, to receive an abdomen expiratory, to the highest level stopped about 10 seconds.', '双手抱头，将身体慢慢抬离床面，收腹吐气，到最高点时停约10秒。', 'Sitting down carefully next to Kaleb, Johannah pressed a finger into his abdomen, which was well defined and gorgeous, like the rest of him.', '旁边坐下来仔细卡莱布，约翰纳塞到他的腹部，这是明确和华丽喜欢他的其余部分，用手指。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abasement">
    <phonetic></phonetic>
    <meanings>['网络: 屈辱；谦卑；自贬需求']</meanings>
    <eg>["In the moment of the deepest abasement of Christ's Human Nature, the Divine bursts forth most brightly.", '在目前的最深切的自卑基督的人性，神用最明亮的规定。', 'Man should know his own self and recognize that which leaded unto loftiness or lowliness, glory or abasement, wealth or poverty.', '人应认识自我，认清导致其高尚或卑下，光荣或屈辱，富有或贫穷的根源。', 'His abasement was the pledge of His exaltation.', '他的自卑是他升高的凭据。', 'There is an abasement because of glory: and there is one that shall lift up his head from a low estate.', '有的屈辱来自尊荣，但也有人从卑微中抬起了头。', "Europe's self-abasement comes just weeks after the last round of Eurozone crisis mismanagement.", '就在欧洲妄自菲薄数周以前，欧元区刚刚出现了新一轮的危机管理欠妥问题。', 'The superficial rock weathering in slope results in strength abasement and rock creeps are key factors that affect slope stability.', '此外，边坡浅层岩体风化导致岩体强度降低，边坡岩体出现蠕变性也是影响边坡稳定性的重要因素。', 'I rise above abasement at the word.', '听着这话，我要从羞愧中站起。', 'He saw the home run as an abasement of the game he loved, a cheap, undignified method of scoring runs.', '他认为本垒打是他所喜爱的棒球赛中最不入流的，一个廉价不体面的得分跑垒方法。', 'The characteristics of kafkaesque s personality mechanism was fear and self-abasement.', '恐惧和自卑是卡夫卡人格机制的主要特征。', 'And it was through humiliation, through abasement, through nothingness that David was brought into it.', '大卫被领到宽阔之处，是先经过羞耻和侮辱的。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abbey">
    <phonetic>美 ['æbi] 英 ['æbɪ] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['n.修道院；艾比；阿比〔姓氏〕；全院修道士[修道女]', '网络: 大修道院；大教堂；隐修院']</meanings>
    <eg>['The day after she died, my 4-year-old daughter Meredith was crying and talking about how much she missed Abbey.', '在它死后，我年仅四岁的女儿梅瑞迪斯哭得很伤心，她说她很想很想艾比。', "Prince William and Kate Middleton's royal wedding is to be celebrated in Westminster Abbey in London on April 29 (Today).", '伦敦当地时间4月29日，英国威廉王子将携凯特·米德尔顿在英国伦敦威斯敏斯特大教堂举行盛大婚礼。', 'Then there has been the announcement by Abbey, the UK bank, that it would be prepared to lend home buyers five times their gross income.', '此外，英国阿比国民银行（Abbey）已宣布，准备向购房者提供相当于他们年收入5倍的贷款。', 'The first wedding to take place at the abbey was that of King Henry I of England and Princess Matilda of Scotland in 1100.', '第一对在威斯敏斯特大教堂完婚的新人是1100年英格兰国王亨利一世和苏格兰的马蒂尔德公主。', 'The children come to the Abbey to see Maria. Sister Margarita answers their bell.', '孩子们到修道院找玛丽亚。玛格丽塔修女开门。', 'The 30-year-old Downton Abbey actor seems to have undergone something of a transformation since leaving the hit show.', '这位现年30岁的演员在告别热门英剧《唐顿庄园》之后，似乎经历了某种蜕变的过程。', 'Once upon a time, there was an abbess in a small abbey .', '很久以前，一个小修道院里有一个女修道院院长。', 'After being used to such a home as the abbey, an ordinary parsonage-house must be very disagreeable.', '住惯了诺桑觉寺这样的家，再来到一座普普通通的牧师住宅，一定觉得很别扭。', 'She gave a simple ablution and left the abbey with tears ablaze in her eyes.', '她进行了一个简单的仪式，然后眼里含着闪耀的泪花离开了修道院。', 'The Crawley family and a few of their best loved servants are leaving Downton Abbey behind and heading to Scotland for a break.', '本次圣诞特辑中Crawley家族和一些深受他们宠爱的仆人将离开庄园前往苏格兰度假。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abeyance">
    <phonetic>美 英 [ə'beɪəns] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['n.中止；未定；【法律】(所有权等的)未定；暂时无效', '网络: 搁置；暂搁；缓办']</meanings>
    <eg>['She cupped her hands around the lighter to hold the wind in abeyance and touched his hand to steady it against the bouncing of the truck.', '她双手在火苗边上做一个挡风圈，在卡车颠簸中为稳住打火机碰着了他的手。', 'He also presents evidence that Saddam "had not abandoned the strategy of WMD, merely made a tactical decision to put it into abeyance" .', '他还提供证据，表明萨达姆“并未放弃大规模杀伤性武器战略，只是出于权宜之计，将该计划暂时搁置。”', 'other problems , which had been hanging in abeyance , were brought to her attention for solution.', '前一段搁置下来没有处理的问题，也提请她解决。', "Her mother had her tutored rigorously in maths in an effort to keep rationality to the fore, and her father's madness in abeyance.", '她的母亲在数学方面严格教导她，努力使她凭借理性脱颖而出并摆脱父亲的疯狂秉性。', 'To understand, the mind must be still; the activities of knowledge must be in abeyance.', '要了解，头脑必须安静；知识的活动必须停止。', "The intellect is always held in abeyance by the spirit of reasonableness, and still more by the writer's artistic sensibility.", '理智阶级常被合于情理的精神所压伏，尤其是被作家的艺术的感觉性所压伏，而无从活动。', 'When the whole melting was complete it was held in abeyance for a few minutes to facilitate the separation of foreign substances.', '铸铁完全熔化了，他们让它在承受器停留一会儿，使铁汁里的杂质容易被隔离开来。', 'With the National Football League (NFL) in a similar state of abeyance, sports fans are becoming well-versed in American labour law.', '同时，美国美式橄榄球大联盟（NFL）也处于相似的停摆状态中，这种状况使得球迷们对美国劳动法变得无比熟悉。', 'If you really grasp the truth of this, then naturally thought is in abeyance.', '如果你真正理解了这个真相，那么思想自然就停息了。', 'Because these grandchildren do not yet exist, the proceeds would be held in abeyance until these children are born.', '由于这些孙子不存在，其收益将被搁置，直到这些儿童出生。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abhorrence">
    <phonetic>美 [əbˈhɒrəns] 英 </phonetic>
    <meanings>['n.〈正式〉厌恶；憎恨', '网络: 痛恨；憎恶；嫌恶']</meanings>
    <eg>['In private they were less tactful. Taft dismissed him as "a peace crank" ; Roosevelt viewed him with "contemptuous abhorrence" .', '私下里，他们就不那么客气，塔夫不屑地称他为“和平怪人”；罗斯福视他为“狂妄自大的讨厌鬼”。', 'It has given me such an abhorrence of annuities, that I am sure I would not pin myself down to the payment of one for all the world .', '我对养老金产生如此深的厌恶感，我可以确定我不会把罪归于他给我的报酬。', 'Smartly tailored uniforms, an abhorrence of cultural difference, and a desire for racial purity are all of a piece with fascist mysticism.', '量身定做的制服，深恶痛绝的文化差异，对种族纯洁性的渴望，都和法西斯神秘主义紧密相连。', 'The president seems sincere in his abhorrence of corruption, but unwilling to take on vested interests threatened by the anti-graft drive.', '总统似乎确实憎恶贪污腐败，但是他也不愿反贪行动威胁到既得利益。', 'horror; disrelish; aversion; dislike; distaste; abhorrence; abomination; detestation; execration; loathing; odium.', '憎恨；可憎的事物；厌恶；憎恶；厌恶；可憎的事物；厌恶。', '"Your elder sister. " The exterior of mother, in the Mou but flash along one silk is to the abhorrence of this appoint.', '“你们的姐姐。”慈母的样子，眸中却闪过一丝对这个名称的厌恶。', 'Despite its abhorrence of his comments, the festival courts the spotlight as much as any celebrity.', '尽管痛恨他的言语，电影节的组织者还是尽可能向更多的名人献殷勤。', "Paradoxically, Jerry's abhorrence of losses stems from the sad example of his father.", '矛盾的是，杰瑞对亏损的痛恨来自他的父亲。', 'Julia and her friends had a fascinated abhorrence of what they called "Pont Street" .', '朱莉娅和她的朋友们非常憎恨所谓的“庞特街”。', 'His abhorrence for the vague and the general is extreme .', '他极其厌恶表述之模糊与概略。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abhor">
    <phonetic>美 [əb'hɔ:(r)] 英 [əb'hɔ:(r)] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['v.厌恶；憎恨；唾弃', '网络: 憎恶；痛恨；深恶痛绝']</meanings>
    <eg>['Dargis: Well, that makes two of you. Did I mention how much I abhor fox hunting?', '达吉斯：好吧，美丽的城堡和你是一样的，我提到过我多么憎恨猎狐吗？', "For example, its authors abhor Congress's recent decision to give shareholders a say in how much chief executives are paid.", '比如，这个路线图的执笔人就非常痛恨国会最近让股东在高层管理人员薪资上有话语权。', 'At this point in the history of mankind, we have been conditioned to abhor symptoms of any kind.', '在人类历史上，我们已经习惯于厌恶任何形式的症状。', 'Homosexuals often abhor this sort of thing and will also be incredibly particular about the cleanliness of the home.', '同性恋者却通常憎恶这类东西，并且对于家里的整洁度极其苛刻。', 'The club abhor violence of any sort and do not condone the actions taken by anyone involved.', '俱乐部痛恨任何形式的暴力，不管是任何人卷入暴力都不会得到宽恕。', 'We abhor the creeping delegitimisation and demonisation of Israel. But we also believe that the Palestinians deserve a state of their own.', '我们讨厌正在上升的以色列去和合法化和将以色列妖魔化的苗头，但是我们也相信巴勒斯坦人有权建立自己的国家。', 'You shall not abhor an Egyptian, for you were a sojourner in his land.', '不可憎恶埃及人，因为你在他的地上作过寄居的。', 'Muslims in England tend to abhor nationalism, associating it with the British National Party (BNP) and its white-supremacist nonsense.', '英格兰穆斯林憎恶民族主义，将其与英国国家党及其荒谬的白人至上理论视为同流。', 'I will destroy your high places, and break your idols. You shall fall among the ruins of your idols, and my soul shall abhor you.', '我必破坏你们的丘坛，砍倒你们的香台，将你们的尸首堆在你们的偶像的尸首上。我必厌恶你们。', 'Most people abhor the criminal of kidnapping the children.', '大部分的人憎恶绑架儿童的罪犯。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abase">
    <phonetic>美 [əˈbeɪs] 英 [ə'beɪs] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['v.降低(地位,价值,身分)；谦卑', '网络: 贬低；贬抑；使谦卑，使降低']</meanings>
    <eg>['But Jehovah will abase his pride together with the trickery of his hands.', '但耶和华必使他的骄傲，和他手所行的诡计，一并败落。', 'The president is not willing to abase himself before the nation.', '总统不愿在全国人民面前降低自己的威信。', 'For You save an afflicted people, But haughty eyes You abase.', '困苦的百姓，你必拯救。高傲的眼目，你必使他降卑。', 'In former times, priests used to abase themselves before the gods.', '过去，牧师们常常对神自责。', 'You can never abase a person for a little mistake.', '你永远不可以因为一个小小的错误而去贬低一个人的人格。', 'But even the Christians who can abase themselves in front of God , also show their stubbornness in mundane matters.', '然而即使是能在神面前谦卑下来的基督徒，在世俗的事务上却也异常顽固。', 'Abase oneself - make oneself humble.', '降低自己的身分', 'A man who never respect others will abase hisself.', '不尊重别人的人同时也自贬了身份。', 'We should abase ourselves before God.', '我们应该在上帝面前表示谦卑。', 'A man who betrays a friend abase himself', '背叛朋友的人是在贬低自己。']</eg>
    <specify>贬低</specify>
    <classify>数据结构</classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abdication">
    <phonetic>美 [ˌæbdɪ'keɪʃ(ə)n] 英 [ˌæbdɪ'keɪʃ(ə)n] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['n.让位；辞职；弃权；【法】废嫡', '网络: 退位；逊位；放弃']</meanings>
    <eg>["Qadri said he would speak to his supporters around mid-day outside parliament to press his demand for the government's abdication.", '卡德里说，他星期二中午将在议会大厦外面向支持者发表讲话，并要求政府下台。', 'Report it. Great country, no they do not have even this trivial matter? Finally, an abdication of old minister said he had run.', '汇报呢。泱泱大国，不会连这个小事都不懂吧？最后，有一位退位的老大臣说他有办。', 'His deft and skilful handling of the abdication issue raised him in a fortnight from the depth to the pinnacle.', '他对逊位问题处理得很机巧，使他在两个星期内从深渊上升到宝塔的尖顶。', 'It is believed that Shah Jahan was inconsolable to the point of contemplating abdication in favour of his sons.', '据说，沙·贾汗极为悲伤，甚至打算退位，将王位让给他的儿子们。', "We guess that Henry is the person who will take over the company after the president's abdication.", '我们猜亨利就是总裁退位后将接管公司的人。', 'Worse, it is an abdication of our responsibility to our children and grandchildren - and a limitation on our future.', '这是对我们子子孙孙不负责任的表现，对我们未来的不负责任的表现。', 'In such a context, silence becomes an absence, a mark of intellectual abdication , a rejection of humanity.', '在这样的环境下，沉默已经缺失。它成为智力减退的一个标志，对人性的一种否定。', 'The abdication and Hereditary systems are the main ways of the dynastic alternation of Chinese ancient times.', '禅让与世袭是我国古代社会政权传承的主要形式。', 'But even after his abdication, he remained the effective ruler of China until his death four years later at the age of 88.', '即使在退位后，他仍然手握大权，直到四年后以88岁的高龄去世，一代王朝才正式落下帷幕。', "For Wallis Simpson, maligned as 'the woman who stole the King', the Abdication was a tragedy.", '对于被污蔑为“拐走国王的女人”的华丽斯·辛普森来说，退位事件是一场噩梦。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abbreviate">
    <phonetic>美 [əˈbriːviːeɪt] 英 </phonetic>
    <meanings>['v.缩写；缩短；缩写为；简称', '网络: 节略；省略；简略']</meanings>
    <eg>['The clergyman would only absolve his torturers , abbreviate none of his final words which once more called on the abolition of slavery.', '这位牧师只会赦免折磨他的那些人的罪恶，他不会简化最后的话语，它们会再次用来号召废除奴隶制。', "I don't believe it will be necessary to abbreviate any of them, but leave the first paragraph out. It's just a greeting.", '我认为不必缩减任何字，但是删去第一段，它只是段问候语。', 'Please write down the names and addresses of both the sender and the recipient legibly and do not abbreviate or use initials.', '请填上汇款人与收款人的姓名、地址。字迹要清楚，不要缩写，要用全称。', "This breed of snobbish, opinionated Brit (let's abbreviate that to Sob) tends not to have visited the United States very much, if at all.", '这种顽固又势利的英国人（我们就简称他们做势利鬼吧）往往很少来美国参观，或者根本没来过。', 'To refer to and abbreviate the name of a namespace, again use xmlns declarations.', '为了引用和简化名称空间的名字，同样要使用xmlns声明。', 'Is the value of the entity simply to be used to abbreviate a larger text string that might change during the life of the document?', '实体的值是否只是用于缩写在文档有效期内可能会更改的较大的文本字符串？', '50 jade flasks put, the He Chen keeps time of bruise to consumedly abbreviate and just were past for three days, and he then opened eyes.', '五十个玉瓶摆放出来，贺宸养伤的时间大大缩短，刚刚三天过去，他便睁开了眼睛。', 'Traditionally, locals do not abbreviate it to "R. V. " or abridge it to "Royston" .', '当地人传统上不会把它缩写为“罗。村”或简写为“罗伊斯顿”。', 'Bad: It is a bad idea to abbreviate enumerations; the user will have no idea which value to use.', '不好的方法：用缩写表示枚举数据不是个好办法，因为这样用户就无法判断该用哪一个值了。', 'Please explain everything in detail and do not abbreviate your sales pitch.', '请详细说明你们公司方面的细节，注意不要缩写销售场所。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abbess">
    <phonetic>美 ['æbes] 英 ['æbes] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['n.女修道院院长', '网络: 女修道院长；女大修道院院长；女修道张']</meanings>
    <eg>['Most likely the girl was scared by Abbess Shih, for she did not come the following evening.', '被石道姑这一撞破，那女子多半受了惊吓，第二天未曾再来。', "Captain: Fraulein Maria, I don't know how much the Mother Abbess has told you?", '上校：玛丽亚小姐，我不知道院长嬷嬷都跟你说了些什么？', 'Once upon a time, there was an abbess in a small abbey .', '很久以前，一个小修道院里有一个女修道院院长。', "Galahad is reared by an abbess until, at age 15, he is introduced to his father, who knights him and accompanies him to Arthur's court.", '加拉汉是有一位修女抚养长大的。15岁时，他与父亲相见，父亲授以他爵士位，并且带着他去参见了亚瑟王。', 'Then she moved on to Germany, where she was made abbess of a double monastery at Heidenheim.', '再后来她去了德国，并且在海登海姆一个特大的修道院作了修道院长。', 'Twice the Abbess bled Robin for his sickness, but it seemed to do him little good, and while he lay there Abbot Hugo of St.', '有两次女修道院院长为罗宾的病放血，但是这似乎对他没有什么帮助。', "The abbess said the nuns hope the record will touch people's lives.", '修道院院长表示修女们希望她们的唱片能对人们的生活有所触动。', 'A large monastery is an Abbey headed by an Abbot or an abbess.', '大修道院是一个修道院，由住持或住持。', 'Without having jurisdiction, the abbess exercises authority over all in the house, and commands in virtue of their vows.', '未经有管辖权的，住持行使权力，所有在众议院，并命令在凭借自己的誓言。', 'The Reverend Mother Abbess said that the order never sought the deal, but rather it came looking for them.', '可敬的修女长爱比丝表示该修女会从来没有主动寻求任何合约，而是合约自己来找她们的。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abbot">
    <phonetic>美 ['æbət] 英 ['æbət] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['n.阿博特〔姓氏〕；男修道院院长', '网络: 方丈；住持；男修道院长']</meanings>
    <eg>['Abbot Agathon used to say, "Own nothing which it would grieve you to give to another" .', '住持阿加松用来说，“自己无关，它将伤心，你给另一个”。', "The Abbot's foot crunched on a broken shard. He picked it up and turned it over in his hands.", '议员不小心踩上了一块瓶子的碎片，它把它捡起来放在手中细看。', 'When King John heard of the way in which the abbot lived, he made up his mind to put a stop to it.', '约翰国王听说老修道院长的生活方式以后，就打定主意加以制止。', '"Hmmm, " said the Abbot as they reached the heated brass doors of the shorter abishai\'s domain. "Do I hear another wager being made? "', '“嗯…”议员说。这时他们已走近了矮个子的办公室的黄铜大门，“我是不是听到你又开了一桩赌？”', 'Everybody said he looked just like the abbot.', '大家都说他长得像修道院长。', "Keep in mind that this GUI is simple for a reason: It demonstrates three of TestNG-Abbot's fixture classes and a few test cases to boot!", '记住该GUI之所以简单只有一个原因：它演示了TestNG-Abbot的三个fixture类以及一些要引导的测试用例！', 'The abbot said the groups would continue their campaign until the election was rendered null and void.', '吴奥巴答住持说，我们的集团会继续其运动，直到实现选举无效。', '"Mom. . . " , he started to cry, falling into her arms. In that instant, he realized suddenly that the abbot did not lie to him.', '“妈——”他大哭起来，扑进母亲的怀里，这一刻，他忽然明白方丈并没有欺骗他。', 'He said goodbye to the abbot and set out to go home.', '他告别了大师，踏上了回家找佛的道路。', 'During the next thirty years he wrote his philosophical and theological works and was appointed Abbot of Bec.', '在接下来的30年中，他著述了大量哲学理论著作，并被任命为拜克地区大修道院院长。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abbreviation">
    <phonetic>美 [əˌbri:vi'eɪʃn] 英 [əˌbri:vi'eɪʃn] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['n.缩写；【数学】约分；【音乐】略号；〔数〕约分', '网络: 缩写词；省略；简称']</meanings>
    <eg>['And soon OK was to find its place in many languages as a reminder of a familiar word or abbreviation.', '很快OK就在不同语言中作为某个常见单词或缩写词的提示语存在。', 'This latter term would even preserve the abbreviation DSD , but would give it a more widely accepted meaning .', '后一个术语甚至可能会附和缩写DSD，但是可能会让更多人接受这个含意。', 'I looked up the word "expo" in this dictionary. "Expo" is an abbreviation for "exposition" .', '我在这本词典里查到了“expo”一词，它是“exposition”的缩写。', 'The second and more recent sense of the word art is as an abbreviation for creative art or fine art.', '第二个和更近的意义上的艺术是作为一个缩写创作或美术。', "I'm not a prodigy, but people close to me that I prodigies, I puzzled, until they know the abbreviation of comrade is a mental derangement!", '我不是神童，但我身边的人都叫我神童，我百思不得其解，直到后来才知道是神经病同志的简称！', 'which had the abbreviation of her name.', '算盘上有她的名字的缩写。', "If you want one of the 676 possible two-letter sequences, forinstance for an acronym or abbreviation, you're out of luck: They're all taken.", '如果你取2字母序列组合的676中的一种，作为一种缩写，那你注定不会走运。它们都已经名花有主了。', 'Abbreviation a shortened form of a written word or phrase used in place of the whole .', '单词或短语的一种缩写形式，用于替代整体。', 'Cartoon animation and comics are collectively referred to with the abbreviation, in other languages with very few.', '动漫是动画和漫画的合称与缩写，在其他语言相当少用。', 'You develop the locator so that you and others in your group recognize it as an abbreviation for a project.', '你开发了定位，使你和你组别人都承认，这对一个项目的简称。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="aberrant">
    <phonetic>美 [æ'berənt] 英 [æ'berənt] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['adj.违反常规的；反常的；异常的', '网络: 越轨的；畸变的；脱离常轨的']</meanings>
    <eg>['With epigenetic drugs, it is possible to reverse aberrant gene expression profiles associated with different disease states.', '用表观药物，可能逆转与不同疾病状态相关的异常的基因表达谱。', 'Consistent with these important roles, a growing number of human diseases have been found to be associated with aberrant DNA methylation.', '越来越多的人类疾病被发现同DNA甲基化的异常有关。', 'Lateral aberrant thyroid rests may be found that are actually occult metastases with a benign histologic appearance.', '可以发现一侧迷走性甲状腺残余，实际上这是带有良性组织表观的癌的隐性转移。', 'One critical factor of these developmental failures of cloned embryos is the aberrant epigenetic reprogramming.', '异常的表观遗传重编程是克隆胚胎发育失败的一个重要因素。', "I'll bet I knew more about aberrant sexuality than any other virgin misfit in Seattle.", '我敢打赌，我对性异常行为的了解比其他任何西雅图的少女都要多。', '"Same-sex behavior in this species may not be aberrant, but instead can arise as an alternative reproductive strategy, " they said.', '他们说：“这一动物物种的同性行为或许并非异常，但可能是作为另一种替代性繁殖战略出现。”', 'An aberrant system call sequence would be a dead giveaway that the program has a bug or is being attacked.', '一个异常的系统调用序列就是一个程序有漏洞或受到攻击的确凿证据。', 'When bradycardia , aberrant conduction, and premature beats are present, hypoxia and hypoperfusion should be suspected immediately.', '当存在心动过缓、差异传导和期前收缩时，应该马上考虑到缺氧和灌注不足的可能。', 'Aberrant ErbB receptor signals usually contribute to the progression and development of a number of human malignant tumors.', '异常的ErbB受体信号与肿瘤的发生、发展有着密切的关系。', 'Malignant gliomas often have the MGMT gene inactivated due to aberrant methylation of its promoter region.', '恶性神经胶质瘤经常有MGMT基因被撤消的由于它的促进者区域的出轨甲基化。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abide">
    <phonetic>美 [əˈbaɪd] 英 [əˈbaɪd] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['v.容忍；等候；逗留；居留', '网络: 遵守；忍受；坚持']</meanings>
    <eg>['The company has also preferred to leave the matter to the courts, promising to abide by their decisions.', '公司也希望将这个棘手问题交与法院处理，并承诺遵守判决。', "Over the years I abide by the integrity of the company Shou Connaught purpose of serving, the enterprise's rising popularity and reputation.", '多年来我公司恪守诚信守诺的服务宗旨，企业的知名度和美誉度日益提升。', "Over the long term, Mr Rutte said, the eurozone should force countries to leave the euro if they did not abide by the commissioner's ruling.", '吕特表示，在长期内，如果有些国家不遵从这位专员的裁决，欧元区应强制这些国家退出该货币联盟。', 'Mr Orban has said he would abide by any Commission decision on the legality of the legislation.', '欧尔班已表示会遵从欧委会就上述法规合法性作出的任何决定。', "He said he'd abide by all possible consequences.", '他说他将承担一切可能的后果。', 'The agent entrusted to go through the related procedures shall abide by all the provisions of these Regulations pertaining to his client.', '接受委托办理有关手续的代理人，应当遵守本条例对其委托人的各项规定。', 'To secure control he had to agree to abide by a series of editorial standards, to be policed by an independent special committee.', '为了获得控制权，他不得不同意遵守由一个独立的特别委员会制定的一系列编辑标准。', "It is in tarrying in the secret of God's presence that you receive grace to abide in Christ, and all the day to be led by His Spirit.", '惟独停留在神面前的隐密处，你才得着恩典能以住在基督里，整天都受祂灵的引导。', 'And her brother and her mother said, Let the damsel abide with us [a few] days, at the least ten; after that she shall go.', '利百加的哥哥和她母亲说，让女子同我们再住几天，至少十天，然后她可以去。', 'I asked her to abide with me a while longer.', '我请求她和我在一起多呆一会。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abashed">
    <phonetic>美 [əˈbæʃt] 英 [ə'bæʃt] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['adj.羞愧的；困窘的；不安的', 'v.abash的过去式和过去分词形式', '网络: 局促不安的；窘迫的；羞愧的局促不安的']</meanings>
    <eg>['"We\'d have had a young gentleman to meet you, if we had known you were coming, " retorted Master Kidderminster, nothing abashed.', '“如果我们早知道你们要来，就会请一位年轻的绅士来接待你们了，”基德敏士特君一点不害臊地回答着。', '"All right, " said the latter, somewhat abashed, it might be well to do it.', '“好吧，”导演有点窘迫地说，这样也好。', 'Nikki began to feel abashed by his praise of her beauty.', '他赞美着尼基的美貌，使她羞得面红耳赤。', "The child was abashed by his mother's reproof.", '孩子因母亲的责备而惶惶不安；', '"He insisted on seeing you, though I told him you were engaged, " returned the clerk, a little abashed by the manner of his employer.', '“他坚持要见您，先生。不过我已经告诉他您有约了。”店员小心翼翼地回答着他的老板，神情有一些尴尬。', "People who used to be amicable so gaze on me as if I'm a abashed daredevil, thinking I'm bugging.", '过去经常对我很友好的人如今盯着我看，好像我是一个窘迫的冒失鬼，认为我在打探他们的隐私。', 'The fool was abashed and began to ponder gloomily how he might put an end to these unpleasant rumours.', '愚人感到羞愧，于是开始忧郁地思考他该怎样对这些令人不快的谣传做个了断。', 'Amy came in hastily, and looked rather abashed when she saw her sisters all waiting for her.', '艾美急匆匆地走进来，看到姐姐们都在等她，显得有点不好意思。', "felt abashed at the extravagant praise; chagrined at the poor sales of his book; was embarrassed by her child's tantrums.", '愧；为他的书的可怜销售情况发窘；因为她孩子发脾气而感觉困窘。', 'She was abashed by his kindness after she had insulted him.', '她侮辱了他后，他仍是那么和蔼，她感到很不自然。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abductor">
    <phonetic>美 [æb'dʌktər] 英 [æb'dʌktə(r)] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['n.劫持者；绑架者；绑匪；展肌', '网络: 外展肌；诱拐者；外展器']</meanings>
    <eg>['Their abductor pulls over and gives chase, gun drawn, and corners them in a warehouse, but Michael gets the drop on him with a two by four.', '绑架他们的人停下了车，拔枪追击他们，将他们逼进了一块货仓，但是迈克尔用一根木棍先发制人。', "Bonnie Sweeten told a 911 dispatcher she was locked in the trunk of their abductor's vehicle and implied her daughter was with her.", '邦尼·斯威特曾告诉911调度员，她被锁在绑架者的后备箱里，并暗示她的女儿和她在一起。', 'Gait at a fast walking or jogging pace, as well as abductor strength and stair climbing speed, was similar between the groups.', '两组间快走或慢跑的步态，以及外展肌的力量和爬楼梯的速度是同样的。', 'With the decreasing of the abductor loads, contact pressure and peak stress decreased correspondingly.', '随着外展肌力负荷的降低，接触压力的重新分布更加明显。', 'But the changes of the contact area were not significant after Chiari pelvic osteotomy corresponding to different abductor loads.', '股骨头软骨下骨应力也进一步降低。而术后关节软骨的接触面积改变不大。', 'The Austrian girl was abducted at age 10 and held for eight years in a windowless cellar by her abductor, Wolfgang Priklopil.', '这个澳大利亚小女孩10岁时被沃尔夫冈·普里克洛皮尔绑架，随后8年的时光都被囚禁在一个没有窗户的地窖里。', 'There are no bodies, no other clues, and no suspicion as to who their abductor might be.', '那里没有尸体，没有其他线索，也无法猜测是谁诱拐了她们。', 'Law will protect the girl taken in and sold by the abductor.', '法律将保护那位被人贩子欺骗和拐卖的姑娘。', 'The gait improved in all hips without any demonstrable weakness of the hip abductor power.', '步态改善所有臀部没有任何明显的弱点，髋关节外展肌力量。', "Don't put your child's name prominently on clothes or a backpack. An abductor can then call them by name.", '不要把你们的孩子的名字贴在衣服和背包显眼的位置。诱拐者会叫他们名字。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abidance">
    <phonetic>美 [ə'baɪdns] 英 [ə'baɪdəns] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['n.遵守；继续；留在', '网络: 居住；持续；守法']</meanings>
    <eg>['The article is right Europe in all the abidance of body developed the strategy to do relatively analytic overview of the system.', '本文对欧共体的持续发展战略做了较为系统的分析概述。', 'Want to realize human society to be able to develop continuously, the abidance that must achieve economy above all grows.', '要实现人类社会可持续发展，首先必须实现经济的持续增长。', 'The rapid development of globalization came into being increasingly deep abidance to affect to East Asia area.', '全球化的迅速发展对东亚地区产生了日益深刻的持续影响。', 'The abidance of economy of a country stabilizes growth to cannot leave the medium and small businesses with numerous amount.', '一个国家经济的持续稳定增长离不开数量众多的中小企业。', "Article 5The principal of each aviation unit shall be responsible for his unit's abidance by these Rules.", '第五条航空单位的负责人对本单位遵守本规则负责。', 'How should be we answered again, does with promoting international the abidance of marine course of study develop?', '我们又该如何应对，以促进国际海运业的持续发展？', 'As American productivity rise ceaselessly, american economy maintained the abidance below low inflation to grow.', '随着美国生产率的不断提高，美国经济保持了低通胀下的持续增长。', 'Environment Policy: Abidance the law, Reduce the pollution, Recycle, Save resources.', '环境方针：遵守法规，减少污染，循环利用，节约资源。', 'The Chinese think much of the blood realshiop, It has three earmark: strong affinity, transfusion and abidance.', '中国人重视血亲关系，中国血缘代际关系具有亲合力强、传递力强和持续力强三大特征。', 'Abidance Finance controller manage and deal with plant data and reports.', '协助工厂经理进行工厂数据及报表处理。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abhorrent">
    <phonetic>美 [əb'hɒrənt] 英 [əb'hɒrənt] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['adj.讨厌的；跟…不合的', '网络: 可恶的；可恨的；可厌的']</meanings>
    <eg>['The idea that Mr Obama is applying proper standards of justice to terrorists is as abhorrent to al-Qaeda as it seems to be to Mr Cheney.', '奥巴马将恰当的司法准则应用在恐怖分子身上，不但切尼看不顺眼，在基地组织看来也甚为可恶。', 'I have never been a quitter. To leave office before my term is completed is abhorrent to every instinct in my body.', '离开办公室之前我总统任期完成每本能是相悖的在我的身体里。', 'Whenever the wind masterpiece, it is always the kind of indomitable spirit of its own against the wind abhorrent.', '每当狂风大作时，它总是以自己那种顽强的精神反抗着可恶的狂风。', "I don't know why a skinny girl like me has food on her mind everytime. IT IS DISGUSTING. GREED is one of the most abhorrent sins.", '我不晓得为什么像我这样一个瘦得皮包骨的女生会老是想着食物，这样令人讨厌的贪婪真的是最大的罪孽之一。', "But he did not include Levi and Benjamin in the numbering, for the king's command was abhorrent to Joab.", '惟有利未人和便雅悯人没有数在其中，因为约押厌恶王的这命令。', 'AIDS activists feel that this new law would be "abhorrent. "', '而艾滋病积极分子却认为这项法令会遭到人们的憎恶。', 'So the water on the left moves up in order to avoid there being the vacuum, its striving to avoid this abhorrent situation of a vacuum.', '左边的水上升就是为了避免真空状态的发生，尽量避免那种令人厌恶的情形。', 'But I Burenxinkan abhorrent that she was tortured by the shadow of the way.', '但是，我更不忍心看她被那个可恶的阴影折磨的样子。', '"They could be performing a perfect procedure, but you would consider it abhorrent that they were cutting a person open, " she said.', '她说，“他们可能正在做一场完美的手术，但你会认为他们将人体切开是很件恐怖的事。”', "He writes that nine out of ten persons in the population were affected by some of this country's abhorrent diseases.", '他写道，每十个人中就有九个得过那让人憎恶的疾病。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abet">
    <phonetic>美 英 [ə'bet] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['v.支持；教唆；唆使；助长', '网络: 帮助；煽动；怂恿']</meanings>
    <eg>['Such a theology could actually abet the good, increase the chances of a happy ending.', '这样神学能实际上教唆好，增加一个愉快的结尾的机会。', 'People-smuggling is done with the consent of those involved; they have no further debt to the gangsters who abet them once they arrive.', '人口走私活动是经偷渡者允许进行的，一旦到达目的地就与怂恿他们偷渡的蛇头互不相欠了。', 'Attempted analyses of concepts in terms of necessary and sufficient conditions, even where they fail, abet discovery.', '试图从必要条件和充分条件的角度来分析概念，即便失败了，也能有所发现。', 'More abhorrent is to connect shading very small also by abet unkennel, came to even that stain dog also be disinclined look you are one.', '更可恶的是连黑斑小不点儿也被教唆出洞，就连那斑点狗来了也懒得瞧你一眼。', 'abet: to help, encourage, or support someone in a criminal act.', '解说：教唆（犯罪），煽动，怂恿；支持，帮助，鼓励。', '"Abet" is usually found in "aid and abet" .', '“教唆”经常用在“怂恿并教唆”短语中。', "The vigorous tour activities promote consumption, flourish economy, enrich people's life, and abet luxury as well.", '同时，旅游活动的勃兴促进了消费，繁荣了经济，丰富了人民生活，但也助长了奢侈之风。', 'Mast cells may also incite or abet conditions as diverse as atherosclerosis, rheumatoid arthritis, autism, and migraines.', '肥大细胞也可能为多种疾病的产生和发作创造条件，如动脉硬化、风湿性关节炎、孤独症和偏头疼。', "That's meant lower costs and faster trading, but it has also helped aid and abet the current crisis.", '这意味着低花费和更快的交易，但它同时也怂恿并教唆了当前的危机。', 'Finally I put forward the concept and abet the crime of constituent elements, and their differences with the relevant charges.', '最后笔者提出了唆罪的概念和构成要件，及其与相关罪名的区别。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abduct">
    <phonetic>美 [æbˈdʌkt] 英 [æb'dʌkt] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['v.绑架；劫持；【医】外转；使外展', '网络: 诱拐；拐走；拐骗']</meanings>
    <eg>['Urban underground tunnel was originally built for legitimate things, but it has been used to abduct people looters.', '城市地下的地道本来是为了合法事物建造的，但却被劫掠者用来绑架人。', 'was to abduct Mary and take her to his grim castle in Dunbar.', '是把玛丽劫持到他在邓巴那可怕的城堡', 'It is a Sisyphean mission, and a dangerous one: the system encourages security officers to abduct and punish the petitioners.', '这是个永远走不到头的使命，也是个危险的使命：体系怂恿安保人员劫持并惩罚上访者。', "You know, brigandage don't abduct women who were worthless.", '你知道强盗不会挟持没有价值的女人。', "While they're incapacitated, Michael and Sara abduct Christina and bundle her into the trunk of his car.", '当他们神志不清时，迈可和莎拉绑架了克里斯蒂娜，把她塞入迈可的车尾箱里。', 'The equation is clear: you are killed as you kill and abducted as you abduct, and as you damage our security we damage your security.', '这个等式显而易见：你们因杀人而被杀，你们因绑架他人而被绑架，你们破坏了我们的安全，我们就破坏你们的安全。', 'Are you looking for a sense of security, if or when the aliens return to abduct you for the firsttimeor the next time?', '你是否在寻找一种安全感？或者，外星人返回地球，初次或下次对你进行绑架？。', 'The cyborg general of the droid army led a bold strike against Coruscant, and managed to abduct the Chancellor.', '那位机器人军队的半机器人将军率军向科洛桑发动大胆的进攻，设法绑架了议长。', 'The news that we see those use network abduct children sometimes filled with apprehension.', '我们有时看到那些利用网络诱拐儿童的新闻都心惊肉跳。', 'The subordinate wolf may also abduct its rear leg to allow for anogenital inspection by the dominant wolf.', '从属地位的狼也可能会被领头狼强行的抬起后腿进行肛门与生殖器官的检查。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abiding">
    <phonetic>美 [ə'baɪdɪŋ] 英 [ə'baɪdɪŋ] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['adj.〔书面语〕持久的；永久的；由来已久的', '网络: 持久不变的；住在主里；容忍']</meanings>
    <eg>["There was just one problem, which hadn't occurred to his handlers - Uri was a vegetarian with an abiding respect for all life.", '只是有一点是其上司没有想到的——尤里是个历来尊重一切生命的素食主义者。', 'Dining room ground handling for the milky white tiles easy to take care of, in the law-abiding, in a few more lighter.', '客厅餐厅地面处理为乳白色的地砖便于打理，在中规中矩中多了一些轻松的话题。', 'If I have been critical, it is only to share with you my faith and abiding belief in both music and young people.', '如果我苛刻，那只是我在与你分享我对音乐对年轻人的信念和坚定的信心。', "Samuelson's desire to carve a role for economics in contemporary policy debates was the other abiding theme of his career.", '让经济学在当代政策辩论中扮演某种角色，是贯穿萨缪尔森事业生涯的另一个主题。', 'There seem to be economic benefits for a society where people are law-abiding, trustworthy, caring and generally nice.', '一个社会如果人人守法、诚信、相互关爱和普遍正派，看上去是有经济价值的。', 'XX: YY, this ring I give you as a sign of my constant faith and abiding love. With all that I am, and that I have, I honour you.', '我为你戴上这枚戒指，作为我不变的信心和持久的爱的记号，我以我的说是所有，尊荣你。', 'Like I said, I normally do not hassle otherwise law abiding gun owners.', '就像我说的，我一般不会麻烦守法枪主。', 'And from thence to Philippi, which is the chief city of that part of Macedonia, and a colony: and we were in that city abiding certain days.', '从那里来到腓立比，就是马其顿这一方的头一个城。也是罗马的驻防城。我们在这城里住了几天。', 'VERY little literary fiction has been written about the financial crisis in Britain. And yet the City is of abiding interest.', '极少文学小说谈及英国的金融危机，可是伦敦城给人永久的兴趣。', 'He was a semi-professional pianist, and his love for music and harmony was an abiding inspiration.', '他是一个半职业化的钢琴师。他对于音乐与和谐的热爱，一直都启发着我们。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="aberration">
    <phonetic>美 英 [ˌæbə'reɪʃ(ə)n] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['n.偏差；反常；误差；一时的记错', '网络: 像差；色差；象差']</meanings>
    <eg>['One of the principal limitations of these lenses is abundant chromatic aberration that prohibits broadband use without design compensation.', '用作透镜，在原理上色差非常大，若不在设计上做出补偿，则会限制其在宽波段上使用。', 'For most of the last century it was thought to be an aberration from the norm that could be "corrected" , rather than a natural state.', '在上个世纪的大半时间里，同性恋被认为是违背常理可以被纠正的，而并非是一种自然状态。', "Direct democracy in California is thus an aberration. It has no safeguards against Madison's tyranny of the majority.", '因此，加州的直接民主超越常规，它对麦迪逊担心的多数人的暴政没有任何防卫。', 'In a moment of aberration , he almost agreed to let the younger man move in with him .', '他一时糊涂，差点答应让那小子搬进来一起住。', 'She said Americans want to be judged by what they are as a nation and not by an aberration like the Quran furor.', '她说，美国人希望世人能够把美国作为一个国家、而不是以《可兰经》风波这样的异常事件来做出评判。', 'To experience conflict is not to deal with an aberration, but a permanent fact of life we often do a good job of conveniently ignoring.', '感受矛盾并不是为了对付某个反常现象，而是一个永恒的人生现实——我们往往为了省事而忽视这个现实。', 'While Mr Murdoch said he accepted ultimate blame for the misconduct at his company, he described the News of the World as "an aberration" .', '默多克表示自己为公司的过错承担最终责任，但他称《世界新闻报》为“迷途者”。', 'At the time I was astonished by what appeared to me to be his complete mental aberration.', '当时我感到惊讶的是在我看来完全是他的精神失常。', 'M. Mabeuf, pale, haggard, his eyes lighted up with the mournful flame of aberration, raised the flag above his head and repeated.', '马白夫先生，脸气白了，眼里冒着悲愤躁急的火焰，把红旗高举在头顶上，再一次喊道。', 'He felt himself to be an aberration, born with a love for learning in a family absorbed in simply scrambling to get by, day to day.', '他觉得自己是个异数，家人们日复一日只顾着谋生，他却天生好学。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
  <word show="abate">
    <phonetic>美 [ə'beɪt] 英 [ə'beɪt] </phonetic>
    <meanings>['v.减少', '网络: 减轻；减弱；降低']</meanings>
    <eg>['Analysts said the improvement around the world suggested that the recessionary forces buffeting the global economy were starting to abate.', '分析师表示，全球制造业活动的改善显示，冲击全球经济的衰退力量已开始消退。', 'Her husband Emil Abate says his family in California would not have objected to his marrying a woman of any race.', '她丈夫爱米尔·阿贝托称他在加州的家人不会反对他和任何种族的人结婚。', 'Mike Geoghegan, chief executive, said the rise in UK insolvencies looked "unlikely to abate" in the medium term.', '汇丰银行首席执行官纪勤（MikeGeoghegan）表示，看起来在中期内英国破产案的升势“不太可能减缓”。', '"Those are the securities most vulnerable to some sort of change" , said Joseph Abate, strategist at Barclays Capital.', '巴克莱资本策略师约瑟夫•阿倍特（JosephAbate）指出：“如果出现某种变化，那些债券是最容易受到冲击的。”', 'Alibaba is taking move abate China foreign trade glides the menace of pair of its business.', '阿里巴巴正在采取举措减弱中国外贸下滑对其业务的威胁。', 'InSenilePeriod, as the general consenescence of airframe, central nervous system also increasingly abate.', '在老年期，随着机体的一般衰老，中枢神经系统亦日益减弱。', 'The function of lubricant is to abate friction between parts of a machine.', '润滑剂的作用是减轻机器零件之间的摩擦。', "An amendment changing a corporation's name does not abate a proceeding brought by or against the corporation in its former name.", '改变公司名称的修订条文并不撤消公司以以前的名称提起的程序或以公司过去的名称对公司提起的一项程序。', 'When resin bolt is used in soft broken tunnel roof, it is extremely easy to create the glue abate.', '松软破碎的巷道顶板在使用树脂锚杆支护时，极易造成粘结失效现象。', 'As the rains abate, for now at least, the political deluge has begun.', '当雨势逐渐减缓，至少现在如此，政治风暴已悄悄地展开。']</eg>
    <specify></specify>
    <classify></classify>
  </word>
</wordlist>
